Game of Thrones 1x10
Fire and Blood
Original Air Date on June 19, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Look at me.
Look at me!
Do you remember
me now, boy, eh?
Remember me?
There's a bright boy.
You'll be coming
with me, boy,
and you'll be keeping
your mouth shut.
- Keep your mouth shut, boy.
- I'm not a boy!
You're not a smart boy,
is that what you're trying to say?
Do you want
to live, boy?!
North, boy,
we're going north.
It had three eyes.
It told me to come
with him, so I did.
We went down into the crypts
and my father was there.
Your father's not
down there, little lord.
Not for many years yet.
You're afraid--
just like Hodor.
I'm not afraid of some hole
in the ground.
You've lived beyond the Wall.
What are you scared of?
I'm a crippled boy
and I'm willing to go.
That's my grandfather
Lord Rickard.
He was burned alive
by the Mad King Aerys.
That's Lyanna,
my father's sister.
King Robert was
supposed to marry her,
but Rhaegar Targaryen
kidnapped her.
Robert started a war
to win her back.
He killed Rhaegar,
but she died anyway.
That's where
I saw father.
You see?
He's not here.
-Here, Shaggydog.
-Rickon!
That beast
is supposed to be
chained in the kennels!
- He doesn't like chains.
- What are you doing down here?
- Come back up with us.
- No, I came to see father.
How many times have I told you?
He's in King's Landing
with Sansa and Arya.
He was down here.
I saw him.
Saw him when?
Last night,
when I was sleeping.
Here, Shaggydog.
You both miss him.
It's only natural
he should be in your thoughts
and dreams,
but that doesn't mean that--
Bran...
- My Lady.
My Lady.
Robb.
Robb!
You've ruined your sword.
Shh shh.
- Shh.
- I'll kill them all--
--Every one of them.
I will kill them all.
My boy.
They have your sisters.
We have to get
the girls back.
And then we will
kill them all.
♪ the boar's great tusks,
they boded ill ♪
♪ for good
King Robert's health ♪
♪ and the beast was
every bit as fat ♪
♪ as Robert was himself ♪
♪ but our brave King cried,
"Do your worst!
♪ I'll have
your ugly head! ♪
♪ you're nowhere near
as murd'rous as ♪
♪ the lion in my bed" ♪
♪ King Robert
lost his battle and ♪
♪ he failed
his final test ♪
♪ the lion ripped
his balls off ♪
♪ and ♪
♪ the boar
did all the rest. ♪
Very amusing.
Isn't it a funny song?
Thank you
for your rendition.
I imagine it was even better
received at that tavern.
I'm so sorry,
Your Grace.
I'll never sing it again,
I swear.
Tell me,
which do you favor:
Your fingers
or your tongue?
Your Grace?
Fingers
or your tongue?
If you got to keep one,
which would it be?
I-- I--
or I could just
cut your throat.
Every man needs hands,
Your Grace.
Good.
- Tongue it is.
- Your Grace, please.
I won't sing--
Your Grace.
Ser Ilyn,
who better than you
- to carry out the sentence?
- I beg you!
Please no.
No!
Your Grace, please.
I beg you, I will never sing again!
- I'm done for the day.
- No-oooo!
I'll leave the rest
of the matters to you, mother.
Your Grace, please!
You look quite nice.
Thank you, My Lord.
"Your Grace."
I'm King now.
Stop-ppp!
No!
Walk with me.
I want to show you something.
Do as you're bid, child.
...And as soon as you've had
your blood, I'll put a son in you.
Mother says that
shouldn't be long.
No, please no!
This one's your father.
This one here.
Look at it and see
what happens to traitors.
- You promised to be merciful.
- I was.
I gave him
a clean death.
Look at him.
Please let me go home.
I won't do any treason, I swear.
Mother says I'm still to marry you.
So you'll stay here
and obey.
Look at him!
Well?
How long
do I have to look?
As long as it pleases me.
Do you want
to see the rest?
If it please Your Grace.
That's your Septa there.
I'll tell you what:
I'm going to give you
a present.
After I raise my armies
and kill your traitor brother,
I'm going to give you
his head as well.
Or maybe he'll
give me yours.